The Reese Family Papers
Marist College Archives and Special Collections
- The Reese Family, 1761 - 2003; 1; Boxes: 1 - 14 Folders: 1 - 19, 1 - 21, 1 - 32, 1 - 47, 1 - 18, 1 - 30, 1 - 37, 1 - 26, 1 - 14, 1 - 18, 1 - 26, 1 - 36, 1 - 14, 1 - 16, 1 - 17
  - Willis L.M. Reese, 1902- 1997; 1.5; Boxes: 3 - 6 Folders: 10 - 32, 1 - 47, 1 - 18, 1 - 30
    - Newspaper clippings, 1950 - 1973; 1.5.7; Boxes: 5 - 6 Folders: 11 - 18, 1 - 2
      - The Columbia Law School News, 1950 March 27 (Folder 12, Box 5)
      - The Columbia Law School News, 1950 March 27 (Folder 13, Box 5)
      - The Columbia Law School News, 1961 April 27 (Folder 14, Box 5)
      - The Columbia Law School News, 1965 March 23 (Folder 15, Box 5)
      - The Columbia Law School News, 1970 December 2 (Folder 16, Box 5)
      - Clippings concerning Willis Reese, various (Folder 17, Box 5)
      - Clippings concerning Willis Reese, various (Folder 18, Box 5)
      - Clippings, various (Folder 1, Box 6)
      - Clippings, various (Folder 2, Box 6)
    - Miscellany, 1902 - 1997; 1.5.8; Box: 6 Folders: 3 - 30
      - Newspaper clipping on the death of Brigadier General Robert Shaw Oliver with photo, circa 1935 (Folder 3, Box 6)
      - Tennis Accolades, circa 1960s (Folder 4, Box 6)
      - Dinner for the retirement of Honorable Abraham R. Lawrence, 1902 (Folder 5, Box 6)
      - Retirement of Percy Preston, circa 1972 (Folder 6, Box 6)
      - Envelope with Bar admission application as well as book on the Pentagon, undated (Folder 7, Box 6)
      - American Flag Facts, undated (Folder 8, Box 6)
      - War rations of Willis and Frances Reese, circa 1945 (Folder 9, Box 6)
      - Invitation in French, undated (Folder 10, Box 6)
      - Invitation to Lunch from Mrs. Howard Davis and Mrs. Oliver G. Stonington, circa 1964 (Folder 11, Box 6)
      - Essex Fox Hounds, 1935 (Folder 12, Box 6)
      - Note attached to 200,000 Mark note from 1923, 1970 June 19 (Folder 13, Box 6)
      - Article on Albert Gallatin, ancestor of Frances Reese from the Historic Pennsylvania Leaflet, 1962 (Folder 14, Box 6)
      - Document in Urdu, undated (Folder 15, Box 6)
      - Ordainment of Thomas Mitchell Dustan and Gerald Early Moffatt, 1943 (Folder 16, Box 6)
      - Invitation to the Inauguration of Richard M. Nixon, 1973 (Folder 17, Box 6)
      - Letter from Joseph M. Sokol, Executive Director of the Five Towns Community Trust, 1959 (Folder 18, Box 6)
      - Commencement Exercises of the Garrison Forest School, 1958 (Folder 19, Box 6)
      - Celebration of the 75th Anniversary of the Lawrence School, 1966 June 4 (Folder 20, Box 6)
      - Dinner menu with sketch of Willis Reese on back, undated (Folder 21, Box 6)
      - “Century Plus” Club certificate of Willis Reese for supporting the Boy Scouts of America, circa 1973 (Folder 22, Box 6)
      - Highway map showing the opening of the Bear Mountain Bridge, the only highway crossing of the Hudson River south of Albany, circa 1924 (Folder 23, Box 6)
      - Invitation to the 50th Anniversary of Mr. and Mrs. John J. Corell, 1951 (Folder 24, Box 6)
      - Ye Occasional Idler, circa 1953 (Folder 25, Box 6)
      - November 1997 - Newsletter (Folder 26, Box 6)
      - Stationary from Stonehouse Farm, Guernsey Cattle, Mr. and Mrs. F.K. Stevens [Francis Kerby?], undated (Folder 27, Box 6)
      - Stationary from the Estate of George Bliss, undated (Folder 28, Box 6)
      - Memorial Service for Willis L.M. Reese at Columbia University, 1990 September 27 (Folder 29, Box 6)
      - Object: Champagne glass, labeled “Groom”, undated (Folder 30, Box 6)
  - Frances Stevens Reese, 1965 - 2003; 1.6; Boxes: 6 - 14 Folders: 31 - 47, 1 - 26, 1 - 14, 1 - 18, 1 - 26, 1 - 36, 1 - 14, 1 - 16, 1 - 17
    Series contains correspondence, environmentalism matierlas, club materials, newspaper clippings, wiritngs, and miscellany.
    - Correspondence, 1966 - 2003; 1.6.1; Boxes: 6 - 7 Folders: 31 - 47, 1 -12
      - Bill and Dora, 2002 July 8 (Folder 31, Box 6)
      - George Boyd V, President of the New York Society of Cincinnati, 2000 - 2002 (Folder 32, Box 6)
      - Alice Osborn Breese, 2002 November 14 (Folder 33, Box 6)
      - Reverend Canon and Mrs. Elliot Lindsley, 2003 January 6 (Folder 34, Box 6)
      - C. Whitney and Emily Dall, undated (Folder 35, Box 6)
      - Nancy P. Durr, 2002 November 18 (Folder 36, Box 6)
      - Robert L. Edwards, undated (Folder 37, Box 6)
      - (Paul and Pat) P. J. G., 2003 May 9 (Folder 38, Box 6)
      - Mary D. Gray, “Doughty”, 1992 August 24 (Folder 39, Box 6)
      - “Marc,” M. A. H., undated (Folder 40, Box 6)
      - Allene and Alden Hatch, 1967 (Folder 41, Box 6)
      - Mary Hoppin, 1991 August 28 (Folder 42, Box 6)
      - T. B. Kinkead, circa 1948 (Folder 43, Box 6)
      - Life Magazine, undated (Folder 44, Box 6)
      - “Marge” [?], undated (Folder 45, Box 6)
      - Aunt Marni, undated (Folder 46, Box 6)
      - “Mary”, undated (Folder 47, Box 6)
      - The Earl of Mino (Gibby), 2002 October 11 (Folder 1, Box 7)
      - Donald Neiman, 2003 April 18 (Folder 2, Box 7)
      - Mary Stevens Otis, 2002 - 2003 (Folder 3, Box 7)
      - “Peggy” with photographic in File 8.2.7.71.55, 1945 (Folder 4, Box 7)
      - John and Grace Pechenx, 1970 March 14 (Folder 5, Box 7)
      - Herman G. Place, 1966 March 24 (Folder 6, Box 7)
      - Augusta Bliss Reese - “Crissy”, undated (Folder 7, Box 7)
      - John and Connie Schultz, 1995 February 7 (Folder 8, Box 7)
      - Trinity College, concerning Augusta Reese, 1987 November (Folder 9, Box 7)
      - W. A. Underwood - “Bill”, 1985 March 1 (Folder 10, Box 7)
      - Charles P. and Ruth Willis, 2002 (Folder 11, Box 7)
      - Invitations, undated (Folder 12, Box 7)
    - Environmentalism, 1965 - 2003; 1.6.2; Box: 7 Folders: 13 - 19
      - Invitation to the “Clearwater” for a Salute to Storm King, undated (Folder 13, Box 7)
      - Letter to Frances Stevens Reese from First Lady, Lady Bird Johnson, 1965 June 18 (Folder 14, Box 7)
      - The Garden Club of America Bulletin, volume 71, number 8, summer 1983 - Medal awarded to Frances Reese, pages 66, 69 (Folder 15, Box 7)
      - Scenic Hudson - 1999 Annual Report, circa 1999 (Folder 16, Box 7)
      - Marist College - association and awarding of a Doctor of Humane Letters, 2000 - 2003 (Folder 17, Box 7)
      - Albany Law Environmental Outlook Journal, Inaugural Symposium: The Hudson River: Past, Present, Future, 2003 February 26 (Folder 18, Box 7)
      - State of New York Legislative Resolution - Commending Frances S. Reese for her lifetime of dedication to the Hudson River Valley and Locust Grove, 2003 May 20 (Folder 19, Box 7)
    - Clubs, 1937 - 2002; 1.6.3; Box: 7 Folders: 20 - 26
      - The Cathedral Church of St. John the Divine welcoming the membership of Frances Reese [bundled in a roll], 2002 March 18 (Folder 20, Box 7)
      - Colony Club - letter thanking Frances Reese for serving as Governor [copy in correspondence], 1966 March 24 (Folder 21, Box 7)
      - Columbia-Presbyterian Medical Center - Twenty Five Year Club, 1966 May 4 (Folder 22, Box 7)
      - Foxcroft Alumnae Bulletin, volume three, 1937 June (Folder 23, Box 7)
      - The Lawrence School - letter notifying of Frances Reese’s election as Director, 1960 June 17 (Folder 24, Box 7)
      - Poughkeepsie Tennis Club - 1890-1990, One hundred years of history, circa 1990 (Folder 25, Box 7)
      - Winnisook Club in Big Indian, New York, 1968 - 1999 (Folder 26, Box 7)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1989 - 1998; 1.6.4; About X linear feet Boxes: 8 - 9 Folders: 1 - 14, 1 - 18
      - The Times Herald Record Sunday Magazine, cover story on Frances Reese and her involvement with Scenic Hudson and the Storm King Case [copy], 1989 September 10 (Folder 1, Box 8)
      - The Times Herald Record Sunday Magazine, cover story on Frances Reese and her involvement with Scenic Hudson and the Storm King Case [copy], 1989 September 10 (Folder 2, Box 8)
      - The Times Herald Record Sunday Magazine, cover story on Frances Reese and her involvement with Scenic Hudson and the Storm King Case [original - folded], 1989 September 10 (Folder 3, Box 8)
      - The Times Herald Record Sunday Magazine, cover story on Frances Reese and her involvement with Scenic Hudson and the Storm King Case [original - unfolded], 1989 September 10 (Folder 4, Box 8)
      - The Times Herald Record Article - additional copies [original], 1989 September 10 (Folder 5, Box 8)
      - The Times Herald Record Article - additional copies [original], 1989 September 10 (Folder 6, Box 8)
      - The Times Herald Record Article - additional copies [original], 1989 September 10 (Folder 7, Box 8)
      - The Times Herald Record Article - additional copies [original], 1989 September 10 (Folder 8, Box 8)
      - The Times Herald Record Article - additional copies [original], 1989 September 10 (Folder 9, Box 8)
      - The Times Herald Record Article - additional copies [original], 1989 September 10 (Folder 10, Box 8)
      - The Times Herald Record Article - additional copies [original], 1989 September 10 (Folder 11, Box 8)
      - The Times Herald Record Article - additional copies [original], 1989 September 10 (Folder 12, Box 8)
      - The Times Herald Record Article - additional copies [original], 1989 September 10 (Folder 13, Box 8)
      - The Times Herald Record Article - additional copies [original], 1989 September 10 (Folder 14, Box 8)
      - The Times Herald Record Article - additional copies [original], 1989 September 10 (Folder 1, Box 9)
      - The Times Herald Record Article - additional copies [original], 1989 September 10 (Folder 2, Box 9)
      - The Times Herald Record Article - additional copies [original], 1989 September 10 (Folder 3, Box 9)
      - The Times Herald Record Article - additional copies [original], 1989 September 10 (Folder 4, Box 9)
      - The Times Herald Record Article - additional copies [original], 1989 September 10 (Folder 5, Box 9)
      - The Times Herald Record Article - additional copies [original], 1989 September 10 (Folder 6, Box 9)
      - The Times Herald Record Article - additional copies [copies], 1989 September 10 (Folder 7, Box 9)
      - Envelope that contained 16 copies of The Times Herald Record Article - sent to Professor Hans Smit of Columbia Law School, 1999 September (Folder 8, Box 9)
      - Dutchess Magazine cover article on Frances Reese and her involvement with Scenic Hudson and the Storm King case [original], 1998 Summer (Folder 9, Box 9)
      - Dutchess Magazine cover article on Frances Reese and her involvement with Scenic Hudson and the Storm King case [original], 1998 Summer (Folder 10, Box 9)
      - Dutchess Magazine cover article on Frances Reese and her involvement with Scenic Hudson and the Storm King case [copy], 1998 Summer (Folder 11, Box 9)
      - Dutchess Magazine cover article on Frances Reese and her involvement with Scenic Hudson and the Storm King case [copy], 1998 Summer (Folder 12, Box 9)
      - Dutchess Magazine cover article on Frances Reese and her involvement with Scenic Hudson and the Storm King case [oversized copy], 1998 Summer (Folder 13, Box 9)
      - Dutchess Magazine cover article on Frances Reese and her involvement with Scenic Hudson and the Storm King case [additional copies], 1998 Summer (Folder 14, Box 9)
      - Note found with Magazines detailing where to send copies, undated (Folder 15, Box 9)
      - Envelope that contained two copies of the Dutchess Magazine article, undated (Folder 16, Box 9)
      - Newspaper with article on the death of Miss Margaret Meiser Reese, age 97, 1961 September 27 (Folder 17, Box 9)
      - Other newspaper clippings, various (Folder 18, Box 9)
    - Writings, 1.6.5; Boxes: 10 - 14 Folders: 1 - 26, 1 - 36, 1 - 14, 1 - 16, 1 - 3
      Series contains childrens books, plays, notebooks and bundled works, and other writings.
      - Children’s books, 1.6.5.1; Box: 10 Folders: 1 - 3
        - “Daniel and the Lion’s Den”, undated (Folder 1, Box 10)
        - “Mr. Noah”, undated (Folder 2, Box 10)
        - Envelope that contained “Daniel and the Lion’s Den” and “Mr. Noah”, undated (Folder 3, Box 10)
      - Plays, 1.6.5.2; Boxes: 10 - 11 Folders: 4 - 26, 1 - 34
        - Brother Wolf, undated (Folder 4, Box 10)
        - Container of Brother Wolf, undated (Folder 5, Box 10)
        - In Pursuit of Happiness, undated (Folder 6, Box 10)
        - Container of In Pursuit of Happiness, undated (Folder 7, Box 10)
        - In Pursuit of Happiness, undated (Folder 8, Box 10)
        - Container of In Pursuit of Happiness, undated (Folder 9, Box 10)
        - Notes for In Pursuit of Happiness, [removed from Notebook 6 - File 1.6.5.3.12.7], undated (Folder 10, Box 10)
        - Envelope 1, addressed to Yale University Drama Department, contained files 12-26 in Box 10, undated (Folder 11, Box 10)
        - One of Those Days, undated (Folder 12, Box 10)
        - Scenario for Rebecca West’s Return of the Soldier, undated (Folder 13, Box 10)
        - In Defense of Honor, undated (Folder 14, Box 10)
        - The General and his Son, undated (Folder 15, Box 10)
        - Notes, undated (Folder 16, Box 10)
        - North Wind Law, undated (Folder 17, Box 10)
        - Dinner Will Wait, undated (Folder 18, Box 10)
        - Scenario for Jane Eyre, undated (Folder 19, Box 10)
        - Criticism of Miss Quick’s Scenario for Jane Eyre [copy, original found in Envelope 2 in original location, File 1.6.5.2.11.6], undated (Folder 20, Box 10)
        - Poetry found in Envelope 1, undated (Folder 21, Box 10)
        - Notes, undated (Folder 22, Box 10)
        - Unknown Play 1 [connected to Unknown Play 2], undated (Folder 23, Box 10)
        - Unknown Play 2 [original, copy in original location in Envelope 2], undated (Folder 24, Box 10)
        - Doctor in Good Standing, undated (Folder 25, Box 10)
        - Doctor in Good Standing, undated (Folder 26, Box 10)
        - Envelope 2, addressed to Larubert, Miss C., and Dean Gregory, contained items 2-24 in Box 11, undated (Folder 1, Box 11)
        - Never Leave a Man Alone, undated (Folder 2, Box 11)
        - Scenario for People a Genou, undated (Folder 3, Box 11)
        - Bread upon the Waters, undated (Folder 4, Box 11)
        - Unknown Play 2 (connected to Unknown Play 1) - [original location, copy, original document moved to Envelope 1, File 1.6.5.2.10.24], undated (Folder 5, Box 11)
        - Criticism of Miss Quick’s Scenario for Jane Eyre [original in original location], undated (Folder 6, Box 11)
        - Unknown Play 3, undated (Folder 7, Box 11)
        - Notes, undated (Folder 8, Box 11)
        - Notes and Unknown Play 4, undated (Folder 9, Box 11)
        - Tea from 4 to 7, undated (Folder 10, Box 11)
        - Pray be Seated!, undated (Folder 11, Box 11)
        - At Holly House, undated (Folder 12, Box 11)
        - Dinner Will Wait (re-write of play in Envelope 1?), undated (Folder 13, Box 11)
        - Notes (bundled with files 15 and 16), undated (Folder 14, Box 11)
        - Newspaper clipping concerning the Seigneur of Serk, ruled by a Yale man (bundled with files 14 and 16), undated (Folder 15, Box 11)
        - Notes and Unknown Play 5 (bundled with files 14 and 15 in Box 11), undated (Folder 16, Box 11)
        - Florida Express, undated (Folder 17, Box 11)
        - The Highwayman, adopted from the Poem by Alfred Noyes, undated (Folder 18, Box 11)
        - Bartlett’s Junction, undated (Folder 19, Box 11)
        - Joel and Sisera, undated (Folder 20, Box 11)
        - Treason - Mad, undated (Folder 21, Box 11)
        - Thy Flame, Aphrodite, undated (Folder 22, Box 11)
        - Good - Until the Last Drop, undated (Folder 23, Box 11)
        - Out of the Past, undated (Folder 24, Box 11)
        - Jormeline [copy, original found with Notebook 3, File 1.6.5.3.12.2], undated (Folder 25, Box 11)
        - Jormeline [copy, original found with Notebook 5, File 1.6.5.3.12.6], undated (Folder 26, Box 11)
        - Jormeline [copy, original found with Notebook 6, File 1.6.5.3.12.8], undated (Folder 27, Box 11)
        - The Cause of the Trojan War [copy, original found with Notebook 3, File 1.6.5.3.12.2], undated (Folder 28, Box 11)
        - T’is on Slavery Indeed [copy, original found with Notebook 3, File 1.6.5.3.12.2], undated (Folder 29, Box 11)
        - Man, Melancholy and Mirth [copy, original found with Notebook 3, File 1.6.5.3.12.2], undated (Folder 30, Box 11)
        - Paruva’s Love [copy, original found with Notebook 3, File 1.6.5.3.12.2], undated (Folder 31, Box 11)
        - The Courage to Kill [copy, original found with Notebook 5, File 1.6.5.3.12.6], undated (Folder 32, Box 11)
        - Unfinished plays and notes, undated (Folder 33, Box 11)
        - Unfinished plays and notes, undated (Folder 34, Box 11)
      - Notebooks and bundled works, 1.6.5.3; Boxes: 11 - 12 Folders: 35 - 36, 1 - 10
        - Notebook 1 - labeled F. Reese, undated (Folder 35, Box 11)
        - Notebook 2, undated (Folder 36, Box 11)
        - Notebook 3 - labeled Elizabeth Stevens, undated (Folder 1, Box 12)
        - Documents found in Notebook 3, including Jormeline, The Cause of the Trojan War, The Perfect Ride, T’is on Slavery Indeed, Man, Melancholy and Mirth, and Paruva’s Love, undated (Folder 2, Box 12)
        - Notebook 4 - Biology Notebook, Miss Hewitt’s School, 79th Street N.Y.C., undated (Folder 3, Box 12)
        - Documents found in Notebook 4, undated (Folder 4, Box 12)
        - Notebook 5 - labeled F. G. Stevens, undated (Folder 5, Box 12)
        - Documents found in Notebook 5, including The Courage to Kill, Jormeline, On Creative Prayer, Apperception and a large amount of Poetry that was removed and placed with Other Writings, undated (Folder 6, Box 12)
        - Notebook 6, undated (Folder 7, Box 12)
        - Documents found in Notebook 6, including Jormeline, Apperception, notes for In Pursuit of Happiness, an Unknown Prose and a large amount of Poetry that was removed and placed with Other Writings, undated (Folder 8, Box 12)
        - Documents found in Notebook 6, including Jormeline, Apperception, notes for In Pursuit of Happiness, an Unknown Prose and a large amount of Poetry that was removed and placed with Other Writings, undated (Folder 9, Box 12)
        - Documents found in Notebook 6, including Jormeline, Apperception, notes for In Pursuit of Happiness, an Unknown Prose and a large amount of Poetry that was removed and placed with Other Writings, undated (Folder 10, Box 12)
      - Other, 1.6.5.4; Boxes: 12 - 14 Folders: 11 - 14, 1 - 16, 1 - 3
        - Poetry found in Envelope 1 [File 1.6.5.2.10.11], undated (Folder 11, Box 12)
        - The Perfect Ride [copy, originally found in Notebook 3, File 1.6.5.3.12.2], undated (Folder 12, Box 12)
        - Poetry found in Notebook 5, undated (Folder 13, Box 12)
        - Poetry found in Notebook 6, undated (Folder 14, Box 12)
        - Poetry, undated (Folder 1, Box 13)
        - Poetry, undated (Folder 2, Box 13)
        - Poetry, undated (Folder 3, Box 13)
        - Poetry, undated (Folder 4, Box 13)
        - Poetry, undated (Folder 5, Box 13)
        - Apperception [copy, original found with Notebook 5], undated (Folder 6, Box 13)
        - Apperception [copy, original found with Notebook 6], undated (Folder 7, Box 13)
        - Unknown Prose [copy, original found with Notebook 6], undated (Folder 8, Box 13)
        - Prose - concerning Eleanor Roosevelt, undated (Folder 9, Box 13)
        - Prose, undated (Folder 10, Box 13)
        - Prose, undated (Folder 11, Box 13)
        - Prose, undated (Folder 12, Box 13)
        - On Creative Prayer [copy, original found with Notebook 5], undated (Folder 13, Box 13)
        - Religious writings, undated (Folder 14, Box 13)
        - Religious writings, undated (Folder 15, Box 13)
        - Religious writings, undated (Folder 16, Box 13)
        - Miscellaneous writings, undated (Folder 1, Box 14)
        - Miscellaneous writings, undated (Folder 2, Box 14)
        - Writings - newspaper clippings, undated (Folder 3, Box 14)
    - Miscellany, 1902 - 1973; 1.6.6; Box: 14 Folders: 4 - 17
      - Prayer Books, undated (Folder 4, Box 14)
      - Cheque for Frances Stevens from Harry East for $6.60, 1935 November 20 (Folder 5, Box 14)
      - New Jersey Divers License of Frances Stevens, 1936 December 24 (Folder 6, Box 14)
      - Pass for Frances Reese to W.C& A.N. Miller Development Co., 1944 (Folder 7, Box 14)
      - Passport for Frances Gallatin Reese, daughter of Frances Reese, 1956 (Folder 8, Box 14)
      - Church of the Transfiguration pamphlet, 1964 October 4 (Folder 9, Box 14)
      - Bill in Dutch, 1971 (Folder 10, Box 14)
      - A Birthday Tale, poem for Willis Reese by Allene J. Hatch, 1973, June 16 (Folder 11, Box 14)
      - Note cards and Business cards, undated (Folder 12, Box 14)
      - Drawing - written: The Hittites Commanded the Roads from Asia to Europe, undated (Folder 13, Box 14)
      - Are You For Me or Against Me? - Poem from the Cincinnati Enquirer, undated (Folder 14, Box 14)
      - Merry Christmas Bulletin from the Hudson River Valley Council - discusses expansion of Newark or Stewart Airports, undated (Folder 15, Box 14)
      - Unknown letter predating Frances Reese found with her papers, 1902 July 15 (Folder 16, Box 14)
      - Unknown letter predating Frances Reese found with her papers, 1917 January 18 (Folder 17, Box 14)
- The Mesier Family, 1700 - 1891; 2; Boxes: 15 - 23 Folders: 1 - 21, 1 -34, 1 - 41, 1 - 43, 1 - 12, 1 - 44, 1 - 28, 1 - 12, 1 - 2
  Series contains indentiures, materials pretainig to Peter Mesier,
  - Indentures, 1700 - 1891; 2.1; Boxes: 15 - 19 Folders: 1 - 21, 1 -34, 1 - 41, 1 - 43, 1 - 12
    - John Hutchins, wife Hannah of the City of New York and Samuel Watson of the City of New York, 1700 November 16 (Folder 1, Box 15)
    - T. Henderson of the City of New York and Joseph Haviland and his wife Margaret, 1755 November 17 (Folder 2, Box 15)
    - Major Frances Brett of Rumbout precinct in Dutchess County in the Colony of New York and Zachariah Van Vooris [Voorhis] of the same place, 1758 February 22 (Folder 3, Box 15)
    - Stephen Calkin of Sharon in Litchfield County in the Colony of Connecticut and John [Maunsell?] and his wife Elisabeth of the City of New York, 1765 August 20 (Folder 4, Box 15)
    - Abraham Abrahams, Peter Nelle and Elias Brevoort, 1765 November 8 (Folder 5, Box 15)
    - Francis Brett of Rumbout Precinct in Dutchess County in the Colony of New York and Zacharias Van Voorhis, 1766 June 6 (Folder 6, Box 15)
    - Gale Yelverton of Poughkeepsie precinct in Dutchess County in the Colony of New York and Peter Mesier, Jr. of the City of New York [3 items], 1767 April 1-18 (Folder 7, Box 15)
    - Peter Silvester of the City of Albany and Peter Mesier, Jr. of the City of New York, 1767 October 25 (Folder 8, Box 15)
    - Peter Silvester of the City of Albany and Peter Mesier, Jr. of the City of New York, 1767 October 26 (Folder 9, Box 15)
    - Frances Brett of Fishkill in Dutchess County, wife Margaret, son Cornelius and Zacharias Van Vorhas [Voorhis] of the same place, 1768 January 24 (Folder 10, Box 15)
    - Abraham Abrahams of the City of New York and Peter Silvester of the City of Albany [2 items], 1768 April 28-29 (Folder 11, Box 15)
    - Francis Brett of Fishkill in Dutchess County and Cornelius Bogardus of the same place, 1768 June 1 (Folder 12, Box 15)
    - John Wanshaer of Essex County, New Jersey (last will and testament), 1768 September 20 (Folder 13, Box 15)
    - Samuel Sinneton of Rumbout precinct in Dutchess County in the Colony of New York and Cornelius Van Sikline of the same place, 1771 August 22 (Folder 14, Box 15)
    - Jacob Van Voorhis of Rumbout precinct in Dutchess County in the Colony of New York and John Lawrence of the City of New York, 1788 September 2 (Folder 15, Box 15)